What's up you guys? Emma here. I wanted
to jump on and do an update episode.
I've been trying to do these a little
bit more and answer some of your guys'
questions, communicate with you guys,
and of course share anything that's been
going on or anything upcoming. Um,
you'll have to excuse me. I did an
interview a little bit earlier and I'm a
little bit uh my brain's a little bit
fried today. So, I'm going to do my best
to to get through this. Um, but first of
all, I hope that all of you are healthy,
happy, and staying safe out there. And I
just want to thank you all from the
bottom of my heart, for all your support
for this podcast, for this platform, for
the survivors that are so courageous and
brave to come on and share their
stories, and for all the all the
outpouring of love that you guys
continually give me, this podcast, and
every single guest. It's just
incredible. And it seems to be growing
every single day and every single month.
And every year that I've done this, I've
just noticed so many more people come on
and and believe these stories and want
to contribute positively. And I get less
and less negative feedback, less and
less discreditation and invalidation of
these um testimonies. And uh I just
really appreciate you guys coming
together and creating this beautiful,
safe, incredible, protective, and just
loving community around these incredible
warriors who are speaking out. So, with
that being said, I had a couple people
that are new ask me how I got into this
and I thought I would take an
opportunity to reintroduce myself and or
share just a little bit about my journey
for those of you who might be new here
or for those of you who may not have
seen other times that I've spoken about
my journey into podcasting. So, I'm
going to try to keep this kind of short.
I know you guys aren't here for me. Um,
I do appreciate all the love that you
give me, but I know that you guys are
here to listen to the survivors. So, I
don't want to take up so much time and
make this a really long episode, but I
did want to come on and share a little
bit about my own journey and hopefully
answer any questions that you guys have.
So, first of all, my name is Emma
Catherine, as some of you know, and uh,
I've been podcasting since 2020. Um, how
my journey got started is sort of a long
story, but it's also not at the same
time. So, when I was 22, I had moved out
to Las Vegas and I was super poor.
Didn't have a lot of money to do
personal development and things that
could help educate me. And uh, I
discovered podcasts and would listen to
them religiously while I was driving to
all the different jobs that I had. um
which is a whole another story in
itself. U my journey out in Vegas, but
while I was driving, I would listen to
different podcasts and realized how
valuable they were. They were free.
They're easy to stream wherever you're
at. And they are just a really great way
to learn about things um whenever you
have some spare time to turn something
on in the background, which I had a lot
of that. I was in my car a lot. So, I
really got a lot out of podcasts and
told myself that one day my dream would
be to create one so I could help other
people in the same way that they help me
and that I could contribute something
for free into the world that would
hopefully help other people on the other
side just as I had been helped. But I
didn't know a direction that I wanted to
go. I am not a survivor and I didn't
grow up knowing about this stuff. I grew
up sort of sheltered from a lot of this.
I was one of those people that thought
that these crimes were very far from me.
I thought that they only happened in
third world countries. I thought that
they only happened sort of at the border
like how we hear all the time on the
news. And I felt very disconnected from
it. Um I didn't know about satanic
ritual abuse. I had no idea about Maltra
growing up. Even human trafficking
wasn't something that I really was
introduced to. um until I got older and
actually whenever I lived out in Vegas I
would hear that term here and there
because as you guys might know that's a
big hub for trafficking and I did not
know that almost my entire time living
out there. So flash forward to 2020. I
was one of those people who uh I was
still employed but my job was in sales.
instead of driving around all the time,
I was now at home and uh doing my job
from Zoom like what we're doing right
now. And I had some extra time cuz I
wasn't in my car all the time. And so I
started paying attention more to
politics, which I never really had done.
Started paying attention to the news
more and was got very curious about
what's going on in in the world. Um, to
give a little bit of background
information, I've always been sort of a
what you might call a conspiracy
theorist. I hate that word, but it's the
best terminology I know how to use. I've
always really been open to learning
about things that are unconventional.
And I could tell you so many stories of
different ways that I sort of broke
boundaries in my professional career um
with thinking outside the box in
different ways in different industries
that I was in um because certain things
never aligned with me and I did research
to figure out why in so many I've always
been one of those people why why hah how
and never really took things like at
face value. I had to sort of like dive
into it myself and learn about it. um
and came to some really radical and
incredible conclusions as a result of
being my own sort of investigative
researcher on the on the topics in my
life that have that I've been very
passionate about. Um health and wellness
and fitness especially being a big part
of my background. Um I ended up evolving
very unconventionally
in my industries and um did some really
neat things and discovered some really
neat things. So anyways, when I started
listening to the news in 2020, I started
seeing human trafficking coming up more
and it was again something that felt
kind of far from me. So I didn't
necessarily
um understand it in the in the context
that I do now. I understood now that it
was happening in my country. I started
researching it a little bit more.
Come here, Kefi. And um it suddenly
became a little bit closer to me because
I started hearing about stories that
were happening in Vegas. And I'm
thinking, gosh, that's crazy that this
isn't as far from me as I thought it
was. Why didn't I learn about this
growing up? You know, we just hear about
stranger danger. You don't hear about,
you know, the ways that that we know of
now that that parents traffic their
children and that these people end up
being in close closely net communities
and uh groups and around the children um
that typically do these. It's not the
strangers typically that are doing this.
And so
nothing really hurts my heart more than
children and animals being abused. Um, I
am an avid animal lover. I have a very
soft spot in my heart, especially for
dogs. I love my dog with all my heart.
He's my little sweetheart. Um, and uh,
my experiences with babies, I have had a
lot of from in my own family to um,
helping raise a child in my adult life.
Um, so I have just always had a really
soft spot for these very vulnerable
beings in our world. And um whenever I
had heard about these crimes happening,
it just became very evident to me that
uh this was something I needed to pay
attention to and I didn't know why. I
was very concerned that this was the
first time that I had ever learned about
it. So anyways, long story short, I went
down these different deep dives and
eventually like you have on the other
side of the screen, ended up stumbling
on satanic ritual abuse, MK Ultra, mind
control, organized abuse, familial
trafficking, and my whole world
imploded. Like everything imploded.
Everything that I knew changed. The way
that I look at the world was just so
different. I didn't know how I was going
to sort of pretend, go to work and and
and and just forget about that when
things changed and I was back out in the
field. Um, but I did know that this was
something that I needed to help with. I
needed to help share this information
now that I knew it. I felt a moral
responsibility that I had to do
something about this, but I didn't know
how. Like I said, I worked full-time. I
had every intention of going back to
work once the whole pandemic thing, you
know, ended and I was to then go back
out in the field on my sales calls. So,
giving up my job wasn't an option. I
wasn't going to go work at a nonprofit
cuz I was starting to read bad things
about those from a couple of the
survivor testimonies that I came across.
So, I had just put it out. I asked God,
I asked the universe, uh, whatever your
belief is, what can I do to help? Please
guide me on a direction because I am so
heavy right now and I need to do
something, but I do not know what. And
so, as things started converging for me,
I started to have these ideas where my
past love of podcasting
started to integrate with this idea of
wanting to help. Um, one of the things I
was doing was looking for survivor
testimonies. I couldn't find them
anywhere and I didn't know why. Why are
the only people speaking about these
crimes, nonprofit owners, politicians,
the the mainstream media? Where were the
survivors? You know, I had to dig so far
uh on the depths of the internet to find
testimonies. Kathy O'Brien's testimony,
one of them that I've aired on my movie
nights on Tuesday nights, is actually
one that I stumbled on first and that
blew my world open even more hearing it
directly from a survivor. a hit
different in my soul and in my heart
than seeing an, you know, an article in
a newspaper or hearing about this on the
news. Um, it just became very personal
and felt so much closer. So Kathy's
testimony was one of the first ones that
I found and it just ripped my heart
apart and I knew I needed to listen to
more testimonies to understand this
because it was so much for my mind to
grasp that I couldn't simply understand
it from seeing an article and just
hearing a term. I really knew that that
in order for me to have a grasp on this
and to fully understand it, I had to
listen to the people that experienced
it, which makes sense. in my life. Some
of the podcasts that I listened to were
about business, for example. And I
didn't go listen to about or I should
say I didn't go learn about business
from some bum sitting on his mom's couch
in the basement.
I went and learned from people who had
successful businesses that were teaching
others how to duplicate what they did.
And so I never understood like why are
we learning about this stuff from people
who didn't go through it? we need to
hear from survivors. In my innocent sort
of naive mind, I thought for sure there
had to be people out there interviewing
survivors. And uh I was very
disappointed and very very hurt in my
soul and in my heart that I couldn't
find podcasts that were interviewing
survivors. Um that was something I was
like, well, I'm going to instead of
listening to these other podcasts, I'm
going to go listen to survivor
testimonies. And like I couldn't find
them. And so again, these ideas over the
course of a few months just started to
converge and all of a sudden it just hit
me like, why don't you do a podcast,
Emma? Invite survivors on. You're
solving your problem and your
frustration. You're living out a dream
that that you've had for so many years
and didn't know what to do with it, aka
the podcast, and you now have this idea
that you don't see anybody else has
done. So, it's sort of like you could
pioneer something and help get other
people on board to support what you care
about. And so, it was sort of done
there. And the interesting thing was
before I had this idea, months before I
really started digging into this
research, I actually had gotten with a
friend that I knew that was a graphic
designer and I said, "Hey, I want I
really want to start a podcast this year
now that like this co stuff has
happened. can you help me create a logo
and just make it really basic? I don't
know what I want to do my podcast on,
but I'm going to call it the
imagination. And the reason why I did
that was because in my mind that's I am
constantly using my imagination to try
to figure out how to make things better,
to try to figure out how I can be a
better person, how I can make the world
better every single day. I'm trying to
figure out how to solve problems all the
time that don't have solutions yet. And
in order to do that, I have to use my
imagination. And so I had a whole list
of names that I was going to name my
podcast or that I wanted to potential
names. I went and looked all of them up
online. And the only one that didn't
have a million other podcasts named
after it was The Imagination. And so
that was settled and I thought, we need
to imagine, use our imagination to
imagine a better world. We need to
imagine a world without human suffering,
without um without human trafficking.
Even after I discovered that, but to me
it was like, how can we use our
imagination to imagine business in a
different way, to imagine health and
healing in a different way, which was
kind of what I thought I would start a
podcast on, cuz that was what my career
was. But it ended up evolving into
imagine a world without human
trafficking. Imagine a world without
child abuse. Imagine a world where
everybody's healed. And so to me, our
imaginations are the key to creating a
world that doesn't exist yet, to
creating what we wish existed, even to
becoming the person that we wish that we
had when we were growing up. You know,
if you don't have an example of that,
you have to use your imagination to say,
well, how can I do things different than
what was done to me? Or how can I do
this job different than what's been
traditionally done? How can I change the
world in a way that somebody else isn't
doing? And so my imagination personally
has always been a big part of my life
and how I navigate the world and how I
solve problems, you know, and how I how
I innovate in my career and my personal
life. And um especially with this cause
that I knew needed the most attention
and needed the most imagination possible
because there's been so many generations
before me that didn't take care of this
problem that I am now passionate about
helping solve. and many of you on the
other side of the screen are. And so
that was the inspiration behind my
podcast name and it fit perfectly once I
finally had the dots connected. I'm
like, "Oh my gosh, imagine a world
without child trafficking. Imagine a
world where everybody's healed." You
know, all these different ways that we
can imagine and envision together. Right
down to having to imagine what something
like organized abuse is if it's
something that you didn't go through. If
you haven't gone through that like me,
this is something that requires your
full imagination to comprehend because
it's so incomprehensible
that there's no other way to do it. You
can't step into somebody's shoes who
went through that and fully understand
um like maybe you can in other
circumstances in life. This is something
that completely devours your emotion,
your imagination. You have to use your
imagination in order to envision what
something like satanic ritual abuse is
because it's just too much for our minds
to even begin to logically comprehend
naturally. So it just really fit. Um so
that was kind of how I developed my
podcast and I thought I'm going to put
it out there on the internet. I'm going
to ask if if you're a survivor and have
a story, I have a platform for you. I'm
going to create a safe environment for
you to share your story. The key being
safe, non-judgmental, all walks of life,
no matter what. The focus is on you and
your story. And there's no strings
attached. It's not about you having
specific beliefs that have to align with
mine. Um, my podcast is about the guest
fully. Every little thing, right down to
the intros that I do, down to the way
that I podcast, I try to be more of a
submissive host instead of an aggressive
interrogator. Um, I try to create a
dialogue that's like two friends talking
versus like me being some, you know,
really scripted interviewer. I like the
conversations to feel very organic and
they are very organic. Um, I don't
script any of the actual conversations.
The only thing that I write out and take
time to do are my introductions, which
are not for the listener. they are in
the sense of instead of putting a
trigger warning on every episode, I do
an introduction to gently allow the
audience to decide if they can handle
the topic and the guest that's going to
be talking, if they're emotionally able
to listen to the episode, but it's also
a way to honor my guests. These
survivors have never been honored in
their entire life. Um, some of them may
have, if they've been speaking out for a
while, they may have been given
compliments and praise, but you have to
think the depths of depravity that my
guests are speaking about and coming
forward to talk about and what what has
been told and done to them. My intros
are a way to give them a gift of
praising them, of honoring them, of
celebrating them, and of giving them the
compliments, the um appreciation that
they never had growing up. And so for
people who say your intros are too long,
I don't care. They're not for you. Uh
you can skip by them if you want. If you
watch the most of my guests reactions
after they hear the intros that I do,
they're very emotional and touched about
it. And that is why I do them, for that,
for them to feel love and appreciation
first thing as soon as we come on as
they're getting ready to share the the
hardest, deepest, most traumatizing
things that they've ever went through.
My podcast, unlike others, doesn't talk
about the best things in somebody's
life, their accomplishments. Of course,
we do at the end. I I try to celebrate
every survivor by talking about the
things that we now get to celebrate as
they're coming forward as a survivor now
instead of a victim. But as we share a
testimony of of somebody's past, they're
sharing the hardest, most traumatizing
depths of depravity things that that
could exist in the world and um from
their own personal experience. And so to
to be able to start the show off on a a
really high note where they feel
appreciation and good emotion first, it
helps transition the conversation in a
comfortable way to things that are
really difficult and helps helps kind of
take the edge off if that makes sense.
And I hope that does make sense to to
some of you. um especially those of you
uh that do make those comments on my
videos um judging the introduction and
not seeing the big picture. So that is
how my podcast got started and I love
doing this podcast. I didn't think I'd
be able to sustain doing a podcast on
this one topic for this long. Um, I am
deeply both honored and also troubled
that I've been doing this for five years
and that there is absolutely no shortage
of people that I can bring on. I cannot
believe how prevalent these crimes are.
I cannot believe that I didn't know
about these crimes existing until uh
just a few years ago when I started my
podcast, you know, and and I hope that
this can serve as a gift that I can give
all of you just like how I received from
others in podcasts that I listen to. I
hope that you guys find the same value,
the same healing that I do in listening
to these. I hope you understand why
sharing testimonies is so important and
why listening to survivors is so
important. I hope you guys understand
the long form interviews that you can't
fit these stories into little 10, 20, 30
minute segments that even four hours of
talking about some of these stories
sometimes still isn't enough to really
explain
what happens and how all of this
connects in our world and the different
networks that are built through these
crimes and the people involved and the
different layers of it and where it
exists and how it exists, when it
happens, how it happens, who's doing it.
You know, I feel like with a lot of my
guests, I could talk to them for 24
hours and still just be scratching the
surface of their story and and the the
brevity of this. So, there's a lot of
strategy that goes behind what I do. A
lot of thought that goes behind what I
do. My podcast is not a religious or
political podcast. It is not pertaining
to one belief system. Um, this is a safe
space for survivors to come on, not be
judged for where they are, where they
were or where they're going, where their
belief systems are, what political line
or or spiritual belief they have. Um, it
is a way to honor them in full in a way
that has never been given to them before
and to appreciate them for exactly where
they are, exactly where they were, and
exactly where they're going with nothing
but love. Um, none of my guests, if I
were to invite guests on, I only
believed what I did. I wouldn't have a
single guest because every single guest
is so unique and we have something to
learn from everybody. Um, child abuse is
not religious. It's not political. Um,
it is not aligned with one specific
demographic. This is a worldwide
pandemic. This is a worldwide problem.
This is the worst crimes against
humanity in human history that we're
talking about. and it exceeds political
parties, religions, it exceeds any
belief system. It's everywhere. Um,
right down to race, country, you name
it. Like, there's no one thing that this
fits into. Um, and so trying to do that
does a great disservice to the problem
at large. And we have so much to learn
from every single testimony and every
guest that has the courage to come up
and share. So, I would love if you guys
have more questions, if you guys want to
drop them below. Again, I didn't want to
make this a really long episode because
I know you guys are here for the guests,
but I don't talk about myself
deliberately um on the podcast a lot
because I really want the focus
intentionally to be on the guests. They
are what matters, who matters. Um and I
know that again, you guys are here to
listen and to see them and I'm so
grateful for that. So grateful for that.
Um, that's what I want you guys here
for. But I do appreciate the love that
you guys give me and wanted to answer
questions from you guys. Um, and that
was one that I've gotten a few times.
So, I wanted to come on and just address
it and reintroduce myself and share
where I came from in this and sort of
the backstory of my podcast. Um, and
where my passion came from with this.
So, I can't thank you guys enough again.
Um, it makes me emotional
all the support you guys have given me
these last five years, even as my
podcast has been terminated multiple
times off YouTube and other platforms.
You know, you guys always find me and
uplift me and keep me going. Um, I
wouldn't have a podcast without you
guys. um survivors, you know, they could
come on and talk all they want, but
without people listening and caring and
sharing, commenting, um this podcast
couldn't exist. So, this podcast exists
because of you, and I thank you for that
gift of helping bring something I was
passionate about to life. Uh it means so
much to me. Um so, I apologize for
getting emotional. Um, just want you
guys to know that you're appreciated on
the other side of the screen by me and
every single guest. There's a reason why
survivors choose this platform. It
really is a safe a safe space for them
to come and share these really hard
things. There's a reason why a lot of
people have chosen this platform and not
some really big platform that invited
them. And it's because of you. It's
because you guys have helped helped
bring what was in my imagination to
life. and you guys have helped imagine
and bring to life this this beautiful
community that we have here. So, thank
you guys. If you guys could connect with
me on um Rumble, if you're on YouTube,
and vice versa, if you're on YouTube,
connect with me on or sorry, if you're
on Rumble, connect with me on YouTube.
Follow my Substack. I actually do uh
after every single episode, I do a recap
so you guys can read the bullet points
of every single episode that we do here.
Um, it's a a great way to go back and
just keep notes on the key points that
we talked about. So, if you guys
subscribe, it's for free. It's in the
show notes. Um, follow me there to get
those updates. I also do written
survivor testimonies and my own personal
journaling on there um from my own
heart. That's kind of my passion project
is my my substack whenever I get time.
I'm also on Spotify, iTunes. So, follow
me wherever you guys can. Follow me on
social media. I'm on Instagram. I'm on
X. I am on um pretty much every
platform. So, come support and hang out.
Come uh keep sharing these episodes and
following the survivors and donating to
them and uplifting them. Your support
means the absolute world to me. So, with
that being said, you guys, thank you
guys for being here and for sticking
through me through this episode. God
bless you all and we will see you next